<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ACL Anthology</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/</link><description>Recent content on ACL Anthology</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How can I make suggestions or provide feedback on the Anthology?</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/feedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/feedback/</guid><description>We welcome your feedback! The most convenient way for us to receive it is for you to create a new issue on our Github issues page, or to add a new comment to our feedback mega-thread. If you prefer, you are also invited to email the Anthology director.</description></item><item><title>How can I submit corrections to papers?</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/corrections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/corrections/</guid><description>Please read the information on our corrections page.</description></item><item><title>How do I link to publications in the ACL Anthology?</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/linking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/linking/</guid><description>Every paper in the Anthology is assigned an Anthology ID. After 2020, identifiers are of the form {year}.{venue}-{volume}.{#}, where {year} is the four-digit year, {venue} a lowercased venue code comprising ASCII letters and digits, {volume} is a volume name or number, and {#} is the paper number. Prior to 2020, this identifier took the form CYY-VPPP or CYY-VVPP, where C is a collection, YY a two-digit year, V a volume, and P a paper ID.</description></item><item><title>How can I submit attachments to papers?</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/attachments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/attachments/</guid><description>To submit paper attachments, use this Microsoft form. Important: If the file attachment cannot be downloaded automatically (via wget), processing of your attachment will fail. Many sharing sites (Github, Google Drive, Dropbox) display by default an HTML page. This complicates processing of attachments and increases the time it takes. Please manually check that you can download your file via wget.
Attachments are processed at least quarterly, at the beginning of January, April, July, and October.</description></item><item><title>How can I submit my proceedings or journal to the Anthology?</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/submitting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/submitting/</guid><description>Please see our submission guide.</description></item><item><title>How does the ACL Anthology use Digital Object Identifiers (DOIs)?</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/doi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/doi/</guid><description>The ACL uses DOIs to refer to scholarly works persistently in accordance with cross-disciplinary standards. Prior to 2012, ACL materials were assigned DOIs by the Association of Computational Machinery (ACM). Since 2014, ACL has assigned its own DOIs to materials using a convention based off of the ACL Anthology Identifiers. In 2015, ACL had to change DOI prefix due to accounting practices for the ACM.
Prefixes:
2014&amp;ndash;2015: 10.3115 2015&amp;ndash;current: 10.</description></item><item><title>What is the copyright for materials in the ACL Anthology?</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/copyright/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/copyright/</guid><description>The ACL materials that are hosted in the Anthology are licensed to the general public under a liberal usage policy that allows unlimited reproduction, distribution and hosting of materials on any other website or medium, for non-commercial purposes. Prior to 2016, all ACL materials are licensed using the Creative Commons 3.0 BY-NC-SA (Attribution, Non-Commercial, Share-Alike) license. As of 2016, this policy has been relaxed further, and all subsequent materials are available to the general public on the terms of the Creative Commons 4.</description></item><item><title>How can I help improve the ACL Anthology?</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/volunteer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/volunteer/</guid><description>We welcome your contributions! In fact, since the Anthology is run entirely on volunteer energy, we need them. The best way to contribute is to browse our Github issues page (we suggest starting with the &amp;ldquo;help wanted&amp;rdquo; tag, and see what needs to be done that overlaps with your interests or skills. Please also feel free to email the director, anthology@aclweb.org. You might also be interested in our developer documentation.</description></item><item><title>What other resources are there based on the ACL Anthology?</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/related-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/related-work/</guid><description>The ACL Anthology Reference Corpus provides plain text and other metadata for a controlled subset of the ACL Anthology.
The following people have written reflections on the ACL Anthology:
Aravind Joshi Karen Spärck Jones A 2018 paper gave a technical description of the Anthology at the time:
The ACL Anthology: Current State and Future Directions Daniel Gildea, Min-Yen Kan, Nitin Madnani, Christoph Teichmann, Martin Villalba Proceedings of Workshop for NLP Open Source Software (NLP-OSS)</description></item><item><title>What software does the ACL Anthology use?</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/software/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/software/</guid><description>The ACL Anthology is built using completely open-source software, with further developments and customization done by the ACL Anthology staff. The current Anthology website is statically generated using the Hugo framework, with the layout being designed using the Bootstrap library. Font Awesome is used as the icon font.
The source code for the Anthology is available on GitHub at https://github.com/acl-org/acl-anthology/.</description></item><item><title>How can I programmatically access the Anthology's data?</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/faq/api/</guid><description>Please see our developer documentation.</description></item><item><title>Anthology Identifiers</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/info/ids/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/info/ids/</guid><description>Every item in the Anthology is assigned an identifier, called the &amp;ldquo;Anthology ID&amp;rdquo;. These identifiers are used together with the Anthology domain name to form a canonical URL for each of these items, for easy location and reference.
Modern identifier format Everything /ingested/ into the Anthology after 2020 (including volumes from prior years) has been assigned an identifier of the form YEAR.VENUE-VOLUME.NUMBER, where:
YEAR is the 4-digit year (e.g., &amp;ldquo;2020&amp;rdquo;) VENUE is a lowercased, alphanumeric ([a-z0-9]+) identifier (e.</description></item><item><title>Announcements and blog posts</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/info/posts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/info/posts/</guid><description>Blog posts and other kinds of announcements have been moved here.</description></item><item><title>Requesting Corrections</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/info/corrections/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/info/corrections/</guid><description>Types of corrections The staff of the ACL Anthology can process requests for many types of corrections. We generally distinguish five types, loosely following the ACM Publications Policy:
Corrections to metadata do not require changing the PDF. Examples include correcting the spelling of a name or the title. These kinds of corrections are typically made to bring the metadata in line with what is on the PDF, which is taken to be authoritative.</description></item><item><title>Information for Submitters</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/info/contrib/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/info/contrib/</guid><description>This page contains general information about submitting the proceedings of a conference to the ACL Anthology. (For information about the complete conference management process, particularly for ACL conference publications chairs, please refer to the official documentation.) It is intended for publication chairs of main conferences and standalone events, who have the responsibility of delivering the proceedings for all main conference and workshop volumes to the Anthology director. Chairs of workshops attached to a larger conference should also read this page, but should work through their main conference publication chair instead of directly with the Anthology.</description></item><item><title>Anthology development and API</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/info/development/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/info/development/</guid><description>API All Anthology data is stored under the data directory. In the xml directory are the files that contain all the Anthology metadata, in a format described below. The yaml directory contains various other important information.
In addition, we have a Python API that defines objects for papers, authors, volumes, and so on. This is all accessible by an Anthology object that can be access in the following manner. First, clone the Anthology Github repo and setup your environment:</description></item><item><title>ACL Anthology</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/index_flex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/index_flex/</guid><description>This is an attempt at using flexbox for the event table, to make it wrap nicely on smaller displays. Unfortunately, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t really work as intended so far.</description></item><item><title>Help Shape the ACL Anthology!</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/posts/volunteer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/posts/volunteer/</guid><description>The ACL Anthology is a treasure. It is the repository of our community&amp;rsquo;s scientific contributions extending back over fifty years; its engine is nicely designed custom in-house software that still works well after almost two decades; and it has enabled research projects examining topics like author networks and topic shift over time. That all of this labor has been donated by its members further distinguishes the Anthology: it is not a found treasure, but one that has been crafted and shaped over countless hours, as if by a hundred Berninis, holding keyboards instead of chisels.</description></item><item><title>Twenty More Years of Computational Linguistics</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/posts/reflections-aj/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/posts/reflections-aj/</guid><description>The title can be read in two ways. Either I should comment on the past twenty years of ACL (which coincide with the period between ACL 1982 held at Penn and ACL 2002 also held at Penn) or twenty more years from ACL 2002. As you will see many of my comments will be relevant to both these interpretations.
How did I get into computational linguistics (CL)? I did not really get into it.</description></item><item><title>ACL 1993—1994</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/posts/reflections-ksj/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/posts/reflections-ksj/</guid><description>As an organisation, the ACL has clearly evolved over the forty years since its foundation. (Whether, or how, it has evolved in its area of intellectual interest over the same period is a tricky and interesting question.) The ACL&amp;rsquo;s organisational development in the period up to Don Walker&amp;rsquo;s death in 1993 was, however, rather different from its evolution since. This was partly because the ACL&amp;rsquo;s community was not very large in its first two decades, partly because there were only three Secretary-Treasurers in the whole period from 1963 to 1993.</description></item><item><title>Chris Spence</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/C/Chris-Spence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/C/Chris-Spence/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Computational Linguistics, Volume 46, Issue 1 - March 2020</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/volumes/G17-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/volumes/G17-2/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Credits</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/info/credits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/info/credits/</guid><description>The ACL Anthology is largely a volunteer-run organization. We are grateful to all our contributors whose work makes this collection of scholarly papers freely available to all.
Active Volunteers Indexing Lead: A. Seza Doğruöz (Universiteit Gent) Site Development Lead: Marcel Bollmann (Jönköping University) David Chiang (University of Notre Dame) Arne Köhn (New Work SE) Daniel Gildea (University of Rochester) Kilian Gebhardt (TU Dresden) Nathan Schneider (Georgetown University) Marc Schulder (Institute for German Sign Language, Hamburg University) Past Volunteers Animesh Prasad (National University of Singapore) Anoop Sarkar (Simon Fraser University) Christian Federmann (Microsoft Research) Christoph Teichmann (Bloomberg LLC) Hien Linh Nguyen (Facebook Singapore) Nitin Madnani (Educational Testing Services) Martín Villalba (Saarland University) Simone Teufel (Cambridge) Tao Chen (Google) Namratha Urs (University of North Texas) Chenliang Li (Wuhan University) Authors of anthology introductions: John Nerbonne, Julia Hirschberg, Donia Scott, Diane Litman, Sergei Nirenburg, Karen Spärck Jones, and Aravind Joshi.</description></item><item><title>David Karoly</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/D/David-Karoly/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/D/David-Karoly/</guid><description/></item><item><title>David Lobb</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/D/David-Lobb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/D/David-Lobb/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Don Flaten</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/D/Don-Flaten/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/D/Don-Flaten/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Francis Zwiers</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/F/Francis-Zwiers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/F/Francis-Zwiers/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Global Water Futures</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/venues/gwf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/venues/gwf/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Global Water Futures (2017)</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/events/gwf-2017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/events/gwf-2017/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Global Water Futures (2018)</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/events/gwf-2018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/events/gwf-2018/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Global Water Futures 2018, Volume 23, Issue 1</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/volumes/G17-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/volumes/G17-1/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Global Water Futures 2018, Volume 23, Issue 1</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/volumes/G18-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/volumes/G18-1/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Helen Baulch</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/H/Helen-Baulch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/H/Helen-Baulch/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Henry Wilson</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/H/Henry-Wilson/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/H/Henry-Wilson/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Howard Wheater</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/H/Howard-Wheater/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/H/Howard-Wheater/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Is the choice of statistical paradigm critical in extreme event attribution studies?</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/G17-1002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/G17-1002/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Jane Elliott</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/J/Jane-Elliott/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/J/Jane-Elliott/</guid><description/></item><item><title>José Bicudo</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/J/Jos%C3%A9-Bicudo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/J/Jos%C3%A9-Bicudo/</guid><description/></item><item><title>José Guerrero</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/J/Jos%C3%A9-Guerrero/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/J/Jos%C3%A9-Guerrero/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Keegan Hicks</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/K/Keegan-Hicks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/K/Keegan-Hicks/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Kimberly Van Meter</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/K/Kimberly-Van-Meter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/K/Kimberly-Van-Meter/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Marcos Cordeiro</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/M/Marcos-Cordeiro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/M/Marcos-Cordeiro/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Maricor Arlos</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/M/Maricor-Arlos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/M/Maricor-Arlos/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Mark Servos</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/M/Mark-Servos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/M/Mark-Servos/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Masaki Hayashi</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/M/Masaki-Hayashi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/M/Masaki-Hayashi/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Meghan Fuzzen</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/M/Meghan-Fuzzen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/M/Meghan-Fuzzen/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Modeling the exposure of wild fish to endocrine active chemicals: Potential linkages of total estrogenicity to field-observed intersex</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/G18-1001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/G18-1001/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Murray Mackay</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/M/Murray-Mackay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/M/Murray-Mackay/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Nandita Basu</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/N/Nandita-Basu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/N/Nandita-Basu/</guid><description/></item><item><title>On the Linguistic Representational Power of Neural Machine Translation Models</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/G17-2001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/G17-2001/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Pam Law</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/P/Pam-Law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/P/Pam-Law/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Parameter sensitivity analysis of a 1-D cold region lake model for land-surface schemes</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/G17-1001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/G17-1001/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Patricia Pernica</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/P/Patricia-Pernica/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/P/Patricia-Pernica/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Peter Stott</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/P/Peter-Stott/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/P/Peter-Stott/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Ryan Connon</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/R/Ryan-Connon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/R/Ryan-Connon/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Search Results</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/search/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Soil and water management: opportunities to mitigate nutrient losses to surface waters in the Northern Great Plains</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/G18-1002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/G18-1002/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Susan Andrews</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/S/Susan-Andrews/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/S/Susan-Andrews/</guid><description/></item><item><title>The Influence of Shallow Taliks on Permafrost Thaw and Active Layer Dynamics in Subarctic Canada</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/G18-1003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/G18-1003/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Time lags in watershed-scale nutrient transport: an exploration of dominant controls</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/G17-1003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/G17-1003/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Tyler Veness</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/T/Tyler-Veness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/T/Tyler-Veness/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Wayne Parker</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/W/Wayne-Parker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/W/Wayne-Parker/</guid><description/></item><item><title>William Quinton</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/W/William-Quinton/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/W/William-Quinton/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Yonatan Belinkov</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/Y/Yonatan-Belinkov/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/Y/Yonatan-Belinkov/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Élise Devoie</title><link>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/%C3%89/%C3%89lise-Devoie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mobehbooei.github.io/website/people/%C3%89/%C3%89lise-Devoie/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>